# IGOR HAMBURGER

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

⊠ idht07@gmail.com



www.github.com/igor-ht

https://iht-me.vercel.app

+972 52-734-6717

# SKILLS

Node.js JavaScript & TypeScript Python

React.js, Next.js

HTML, JSX CSS/SCSS, CSS-in-JS Prisma, Postgresql, MongoDB Next-Auth, Auth.js Jest, Cypress

JSON

### LANGUAGES



#### PROFILE

As an individual who has successfully navigated transitions and embraced new environments, I have demonstrated **adaptability** and **resilience**. Since 2016, I have embarked on a journey from Brazil to Israel, embracing new challenges along the way with a lot of **motivation**. With a strong **analytical mindset** and meticulous **attention to detail**, I precisely **approach tasks**, always carrying a lot of **dedication** with me. Additionally, my exceptional **interpersonal skills** enable me to excel in diverse settings.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer Freelancer (2023 - Present)

- End to end development using HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript/TypeScript, React, Next.js, Prisma, Express, Node.js.
- Strong SW basic knowledge in Python.
- Database SQL, NoSQL, ORM.
- Authentication next-auth, Auth.js, OAuth, JWT.
- Developed e2e and unit test using Cypress and Jest.
- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Managed projects and repositories using GitHub.

#### **Israel Defense Forces - IDF** 2017-2020

Volunteered and served for 3 years and 2 months in the elite Egoz Unity at the commando brigade of the IDF.

- Developed strong leadership
- Teamwork
- Ability to cope with challenges while leading my team to success.

#### EDUCATION

WebDev - Full Stack Web Development Tel Aviv - 2022-2023

Google & University Reichman - Tech School

The WebDev program provides both academic and practical training based on Google's technical expertise and Reichman University's academic excellence. This Full Stack Web Development program covers the following fields: computer science fundamentals, data structures and algorithms, Python, JavaScript, React, Node.js, SQL, HTML, CSS and more.

**Environmental Engineering** São Paulo - 2013 - 2015 Barão de Mauá University

- Developed a strong foundation in engineering principles and practices.
- Gained comprehensive knowledge in areas such as water and wastewater treatment, air pollution control, and solid waste management.
- Collaborated effectively with multidisciplinary teams to solve complex environmental challenges.